A Guide to the Papers of Ann Beattie
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Ann Beattie 1989-1993
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10414-x
This collection consists of 11 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited 1993 September 27.
Scope and Content Information
Advance, uncorrected proof of forthcoming novels sent by publishers to Ann Beattie for her review. Authors include: Patrick Anderson, Jonathan Carroll, Carol Muske-Dukes, Kelvin Christopher James, Daniel L. Magida, Lew McCreary, Mildred Parker, Annie Proulx, Robert Love Taylor, Lisa Zeidner, and Eugenia Zukerman.
Contents List
- After Silence by Jonathan Carroll 1993
  Uncorrected Proof, Doubleday
- Busy-Bodies by Patrick Anderson 1989
  Advance Uncorrected Reader's Proof, Simon and Schuster
- Hello Down There by Michael Parker 1993
  Uncorrected Advance Proof, Charles Scribner's Sons
- Jumping Ship and Other Stories by Kelvin Christopher James 1992
  Uncorrected Proof, Villard Books
- Lady of Spain by Robert Love Taylor 1992
  Advance Uncorrected Proof, Algonquin Books of Chapel Hill
- Limited Partnerships A Novel by Lisa Zeidner 1989
  Advance Reading Copy (Uncorrected Page Proofs), North Point Press
- The Minus Man by Lew McCreary 1991
  Unrevised and Unpublished Proofs, Viking
- The Rules of Seduction by Daniel L. Magida 1992
  Uncorrected Manuscript, Houghton Mifflin Company
- Saving St. Germ by Carol Muske Dukes 1993
- The Shipping News by E. Annie Proulx 1993
- Taking the Heat by Eugenia Zukerman 1991
  Uncorrected and Unpublished Proofs, Simon and Schuster